<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Machine-learning on SELÇUK KORKMAZ, PH.D.</title>
    <link>/tags/machine-learning/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Machine-learning on SELÇUK KORKMAZ, PH.D.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2021 Selçuk Korkmaz</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/machine-learning/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Quaternary Structure Evaluation Tool</title>
      <link>/project/bet/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/bet/</guid>
      <description>This web tool is developed for evaluation of quaternary structures of protein structures in the Protein Data Bank. There are four different methods for the evaluation process:
Sequence cluster result with a consistency score for each PDB ID.
Text mining of the primary citations in order to extract oligomeric state and experimental evidence.
Stoichiometry and symmetry predictions for quaternary structures using PISA.
Stoichiometry and symmetry predictions for quaternary structures using EPPIC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MLViS: machine learning-based virtual screening tool</title>
      <link>/project/mlvis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/mlvis/</guid>
      <description>Virtual screening is an important step in early-phase of drug discovery process. Since there are thousands of compounds, this step should be both fast and effective in order to distinguish drug-like and nondrug-like molecules. Statistical machine learning methods are widely used in drug discovery studies for classification purpose. Here, we developed a new tool, which can classify molecules as drug-like and nondrug-like based on various machine learning methods, including discriminant, tree-based, kernel-based, ensemble and other algorithms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>voomDDA: Discovery of Diagnostic Biomarkers and Classification of RNA-Seq Data </title>
      <link>/project/voomdda/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/voomdda/</guid>
      <description>Identifying the relevant genes (or other genomic features such as transcripts, miRNAs, lncRNAs, etc.) across the conditions (e.g. tumor and non-tumor tissue samples) is a common research interest in gene-expression studies. In this gene selection, researchers are often interested in detecting a small set of genes for diagnostic purpose in medicine that involves identification of the minimal subset of genes that achieves maximal predictive performance. biomarker discovery and classification problem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DDNAA: Decision support system for differential diagnosis of nontraumatic acute abdomen</title>
      <link>/project/ddnaa/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/ddnaa/</guid>
      <description>A quick evaluation is required for patients with acute abdominal pain. It is crucial to differentiate between surgical and nonsurgical pathology. Practical and accurate tests are essential in this differentiation. Lately, D-dimer level is found to be an important adjuvant in this diagnosis and obviously outperforms leukocyte count, which is widely used for diagnosis of certain cases [1,2]. Here, we handle this problem in a statistical perspective and combine the information from leukocyte count along with D-dimer level to increase the diagnostic accuracy of nontraumatic acute abdomen.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>